<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GW Robotics</title>
    <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GW Robotics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 14:37:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gw-robotics.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW-TO: OpenCV Installation (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/11/08/how-to-opencv-installation-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 14:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/11/08/how-to-opencv-installation-windows/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial is for installation of OpenCV for Python on a Windows PC from prebuilt files. A fully detailed tutorial can be found at the OpenCV documentation.
To Install OpenCV and Dependencies First, make sure that your computer has the right Python setup with Numpy. Matplotlib is optional and is mostly for use with the tutorials. You can check that you have Python 2.7.whatever using:
python -V  After verifying that you have Python 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Meeting 10/29/2016 Notes</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/10/29/design-meeting-10-29-2016-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 11:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/10/29/design-meeting-10-29-2016-notes/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR We talked about drivetrain design.
It was confirmed that we are not using a suspension system on the middle wheels with the H-drive. This decision was mainly to avoid complexity. The issue of the wheels hitting something was discussed and the possible sensors needed to detect that. It was decided that we just won&amp;rsquo;t hit anything unexpected, or use the ultrasonic sensor to detect if we do by chance. It was also stated that the frame will be above the wheels, allowing us to move the wheels to the edge of the size constraint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Arduino-Raspberry Pi Serial Comms</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/10/26/testing-arduino-raspberry-pi-serial-comms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/blog/2016/10/26/testing-arduino-raspberry-pi-serial-comms/</guid>
      <description>Tonight, Nam went through a tutorial on communicating via a USB cable between an Arduino and a Raspberry Pi. Here are a few things to note: - The tutorial did not mention the need to download PySerial. This was done via pip. - The Arduino sketch was compiled via a computer, and then the Arduino was connected to the Raspberry Pi. - The Raspberry Pi python program was written using Nano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/calendar/</guid>
      <description>     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you want to make robots with us?
Please feel free to contact us, and we will respond to you as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Robotics is a pretty difficult and complex topic, so here are some of the most commonly asked questions we hear. If you have a question not mentioned here, feel free to email us.
1. WHAT IS A ROBOT? A robot is a machine that can complete a task that affects an environment.
2. HOW DO I JOIN? All you have to do is show up to a meeting! We meet (almost) every Wednesday night in Funger 223 at 9pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GW Robotics Competition</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/sumo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/sumo/</guid>
      <description>table { border-collapse: collapse; margin: auto; } table, th, td { border: 1px solid black; padding: 1em; }   .button { background-color: #004065; border: none; color: white; padding: 15px 32px; text-align: center; text-decoration: none; display: inline-block; font-size: 36px; }  Register Now!    
About The Competition Robot-sumo is a popular type of robotics competition in which teams create robots of various sizes, with the objective of pushing the other teams&amp;rsquo; robots out of a ring (much like normal sumo wrestling).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>