<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GW Robotics</title>
    <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GW Robotics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gw-robotics.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/standards/</guid>
      <description>GW Robotics Version Control Guide The purpose of this document is to provide standard protocol for using Git and GitHub for version control of GW Robotics software, as well as a quick reference.
Introduction Version control is an important aspect of software develop, providing collaboration and failure fallbacks if done correctly. Proper version control allows a team to work on their own version of a project and then merge them together with relative ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/calendar/</guid>
      <description>     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you want to make robots with us?
Please feel free to contact us, and we will respond to you as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Robotics is a pretty difficult and complex topic, so here are some of the most commonly asked questions we hear. If you have a question not mentioned here, feel free to email us.
1. WHAT IS A ROBOT? A robot is a machine that can complete a task that affects an environment.
2. HOW DO I JOIN? All you have to do is show up to a meeting! We meet (almost) every Wednesday night in Funger 223 at 9pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumo Robotics Competition</title>
      <link>https://gw-robotics.github.io/sumo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gw-robotics.github.io/sumo/</guid>
      <description>table { border-collapse: collapse; margin: auto; } table, th, td { border: 1px solid black; padding: 1em; }   .button { background-color: #004065; border: none; color: white; padding: 15px 32px; text-align: center; text-decoration: none; display: inline-block; font-size: 36px; }  Register Now!    
About The Competition Robot-sumo is a popular type of robotics competition in which teams create robots of various sizes, with the objective of pushing the other teams&amp;rsquo; robots out of a ring (much like normal sumo wrestling).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>